{
    "id": "8a40d64f571d4b62a2269deec03a89e3",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The police officer warned the crowd that he ……………… order shooting, if they created trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a31c05ba833747e084f76b7ffddd3517"
        },
        {
            "question": "Passengers ……………… not smoke inside the bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "should",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc62bc42cf884edcb236d94a26274b09"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I have a word with you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Will",
                "Either can or may"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "de23a3e99c934da5abcd80291208b9b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Parents ……………….. not accompany their children to the school. (prohibition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c044b484a855440f90deb6bb4d36b53e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a time when I ................................ stay up late, but these days I go to bed early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ought to",
                "used to",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "58bb4ab39e57430fa4c1cb38e8e2295d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Principal said that candidates without hall tickets ………………. not be permitted inside the examination hall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9fe52cc3d874df1b1a722ecc0e151de"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………….. tell me. I know everything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need not",
                "must not",
                "cannot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d3e86c9f5f914e22a2934ed078fe0ca8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Even if he had come a  little earlier , he ………………… have got a seat in the front row.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should not",
                "might not",
                "would not"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa26e44046ae4a37a5e86916c78100cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I tell you what happened?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f7dcb5335fb4a999ec93ef6765882a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘How …………….. he leave the office earlier without my permission?’ asked the Manager.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fb83c0085fc44a08b014532ec4999f04"
        }
    ]
}